{
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Who lived at 221B, Baker Street, London?",
            "options": [
                "Sherlock Holmes",
                "George Walker Bush",
                "Donald Trump",
                "prince Harry"
            ],
            "answer": "Sherlock Holmes"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many states are there in america",
            "options": [
                "40",
                "47",
                "50",
                "32"
            ],
            "answer": "50"
        },
        {
            "question": "World 4th richest man",
            "options": [
                "Jeff Bezos",
                "Bill Gates",
                "Bernard Arnault",
                "Warren Buffett"
            ],
            "answer": "Warren Buffett"
        },
        {
            "question": "The slogan for which Auto brand is ‘The best or nothing’?",
            "options": [
                "Mercedes-Benz",
                "Honda",
                "Ford",
                "Vw"
            ],
            "answer": "Mercedes-Benz"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which Fighter Jet Is The Fastest?",
            "options": [
                "Lockheed Martin F-22 Raptor",
                "Dassault Mirage 2000",
                "MiG-31",
                "McDonnell Douglas F-15"
            ],
            "answer": "MiG-31"
        },
        {
            "question": "The most peaceful country in the world",
            "options": [
                "Iceland",
                "new zealand",
                "Denmark",
                "syria"
            ],
            "answer": "Iceland"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which country will host the 45th G7 summit 2019 ",
            "options": [
                "Italy",
                "Germany",
                "France",
                "Canada"
            ],
            "answer": "France"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following is the capital of Arunachal Pradesh ",
            "options": [
                "Itanagar",
                "Dispur",
                "Imphal",
                "Panaji"
            ],
            "answer": "Itanagar"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which is the largest coffee producing state of India ",
            "options": [
                "Kerala",
                "Tamil Nadu",
                "Karnataka",
                "Arunachal Pradesh"
            ],
            "answer": "Karnataka"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which state has the largest area ",
            "options": [
                "Maharashtra",
                "Madhya Pradesh",
                "Uttar Pradesh",
                "Rajasthan"
            ],
            "answer": "Rajasthan"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which state has the largest population",
            "options": [
                "Maharashtra",
                "Madhya Pradesh",
                "Uttar Pradesh",
                "Rajasthan"
            ],
            "answer": "Uttar Pradesh"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which among the following is not a power of RBI",
            "options": [
                "inspection of banks",
                "Nationalization of Banks",
                "Call of returns",
                "Control the lending policies of the banks"
            ],
            "answer": "Nationalization of Banks"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which among the following is not a power of RBI",
            "options": [
                "inspection of banks",
                "Nationalization of Banks",
                "Call of returns",
                "Control the lending policies of the banks"
            ],
            "answer": "Nationalization of Banks"
        },
        {
            "question": "India's largest city by population",
            "options": [
                "Mumbai",
                "Bangalore",
                "Delhi",
                "Kolkata"
            ],
            "answer": "Mumbai"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which state is known as India's spice garden",
            "options": [
                "Kerala",
                "Karnataka",
                "Assam",
                "Andhra Pradesh"
            ],
            "answer": "Kerala"
        }
    ]
}